

# WENXUAN WANG

+86 17621222563 wxwang.iris@gmail.com Homepage Google Scholar

## **SUMMARY**

I am currently a second-year Ph.D. student at Fudan University, under the supervision of Prof. Xiangyang Xue. At present, I devote to the research of adversarial attacks, generative adversarial networks, person re-identification, face recognition, expression classification with deep learning.

# **EDUCATION**

2000.1		
PHD of Science   Computer Application Fudan University	Sep. 2019 – Now Shanghai	
Master of Science   Computer Application Fudan University	Sep. 2017 – Jun. 2019 Shanghai	
<b>Bachelor of Engineering</b>   <i>Computer Science and Technology</i> Northwestern Polytechnical University	Sep. 2013 – Jun. 2017 Shaanxi	

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

## Conference

- Delving into Data: Effectively Substitute Training for Black-box Attack. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2021.
   Wenxuan Wang, Bangjie Yin, Taiping Yao, Li Zhang, Yanwei Fu, Shouhong Ding, Jilin Li, Feiyue Huang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Adv-Makeup: A New Imperceptible and Transferable Attack on Face Recognition. International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI), 2021.
   Bangjie Yin\*, Wenxuan Wang\*, Taiping Yao\*, Junfeng Guo, Zelun Kong, Shouhong Ding, Jilin Li, Cong Liu.
- FMMu-Net: Face Morphological Multi-branch Network for Makeup-invariant Face Verification. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2020. Wenxuan Wang, Yanwei Fu, Xuelin Qian, Qi Tian, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Long-Term Cloth-Changing Person Re-identification. Asian Conference on Computer Vision (ACCV), 2020. (Oral)
   Xuelin Qian, Wenxuan Wang, Li Zhang, Fangrui Zhu, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Comp-GAN: Compositional Generative Adversarial Network in Synthesizing and Recognizing Facial Expression. ACM International Conference on Multimedia. (ACM MM), 2019.
   Wenxuan Wang, Qiang Sun, Yanwei Fu, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.
- Pose-Normalized Image Generation for Person Re-identification. European Conference on Computer Vision. (ECCV), 2018.
   Xuelin Qian, Yanwei Fu, Tao Xiang, Wenxuan Wang, Jie Qiu, Yang Wu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue.

# Preprint

- A New Screening Method for COVID-19 based on Ocular Feature Recognition by Machine Learning Tools.
  - Yanwei Fu, Feng Li, **Wenxuan Wang**, Haicheng Tang, Xuelin Qian, Mengwei Gu, Xiangyang Xue. medRxiv, 2020.
- Learning to Augment Expressions for Few-shot Fine-grained Facial Expression Recognition.
   Wenxuan Wang, Yanwei Fu, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Xiangyang Xue. arXiv, 2019.
- A Fine-Grained Facial Expression Database for End-to-End Multi-Pose Facial Expression Recognition.
   Wenxuan Wang, Qiang Sun, Tao Chen, Chenjie Cao, Ziqi Zheng, Guoqiang Xu, Han Qiu, Yanwei Fu. arXiv, 2018.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Ping An Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019

Algorithm Intern

- Facial expression recognition under few-shot setting project.
- Build a novel fine-grained facial expression dataset.
- Proposed an algorithm of recognizing subtle facial expression in the insufficient training data condition.
- Published a conference paper (ACM MM 2019).

**Tencent** Jun. 2020 – Jan. 2021

Algorithm Intern

- The adversarial examples and the robustness of the deep neural networks.
- Proposed a novel algorithm to realize black-box attack under data-free condition.
- Introduced an algorithm to generate imperceptible and transferable attacks on face recognition system.
- Published two conference papers (CVPR 2021 and IJCAI 2021).

#### HONORS AND AWARDS

National Scholarship	2016-2017
Recognition for to 1% of students in GPA at Northwestern Polytechnical University	
First-class Scholarship for Excellent Master Students	2017-2018
Recognition for to 10% of master students in academics at Fudan University	
'Wei Rui' Scholarship	2018-2019
Recognition for to 5% of Ph.D students in academics at Fudan University	
First-class Scholarship for Excellent Ph.D Students	2019-2020
Recognition for to 10% of Ph.D students in academics at Fudan University	

## **EXTRA**

# **Academic Activities**

Conference Reviewer: CVPR, ICCV, AAAI

Teaching AssistantSep. 2018 – Feb. 2019Information System SecurityFudan UniversityPart-Time TeacherDec. 2018 – Jul. 2017Teaching junior high school students Chinese, English and PhysicsZhangMen, Online

# **SKILLS**

**Languages**: Chinese, English **Programming**: Python, C, C++

**Platform**: Pytorch, Matlab, Tensorflow, Caffe **Document Creation**: Microsoft Office Suite, LaTex